vasundhara.net 2019-06-15

# Vasundara Kutumbam ::Dheera

Vasundhara.net is website of Ushodaya Enterprises Private Ltd (UEPL) aimed at providing information useful for all round development of women. We understand the importance of your right to privacy, hence have a privacy policy for all users of the website with regard to the information we collect from them and other concerns of privacy of the users. For all online transactions we use third party services. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please email to us on “privacypolicy@ vasundhara.net” .

vasundhara.net provides a user-friendly platform for members to post their views, opinions and to participate in interactive programmes run by Ushodaya Enterprises Private Limited on the website. To facilitate the membership, we request prospective members to provide certain personal information. However the information collected from any of our members is not shared with any individual or organization without the formers approval.

All vasundhara.net visitors will be able to browse the site, view articles or features posted on our site, without entering any personal information. Some of the essential information gathered from members and guests who seek to participate in any inter-active programme on vasundhara.net includes, but may not be limited to, email address, first name, last name, a user-specified password, mailing address, pin code, mobile number, telephone number or fax number. 

If members wish to subscribe for paid services which may be offered by us, we may collect some additional information from them, including a billing address, a credit card number and a credit card expiration date and tracking information. This information collected from members is NOT shared:

The information gathered from vasundhara.net members is shared only with the consent of the member, with any individual or organization. Members registering on "vasundhara.net" shall be automatically consenting for receiving calls or Text Messages from vasundhara.net. Except where members are expressly informed, vasundhara.net does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. All information provided by members is held with the utmost care and security. However, vasundhara.net is also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.

To extend the benefits and services on vasundhara.net, we may tie-up with third parties/partners. However, vasundhara.net will share only such of your personal information as may be necessary.

####  All visitors need NOT pay:

Visitors of vasundhara.net may browse the site, view any articles or features our site has to offer without entering any personal information or paying money.

####  Links to external websites:

vasundhara.net may contain links to external websites. vasundhara.net shall not be responsible for the privacy practices of external Web sites and users are advised to check the privacy policy of such third party websites. We request you to be fully aware of this when you leave vasundhara.net. Do read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.  
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by vasundhara.net

####  Cookies on vasundhara.net:

Cookies on vasundhara.net are used to deliver various services and keep track of your personal preferences. If you do not want cookies to collect information on vasundhara.net, most browsers contain a function that allows a user to deny cookies on websites. Alternatively you can also delete all cookie files on your computer. Please note that disabling the cookie feature on your browser or deleting cookie files from your computer will render you unable to access certain features on vasundhara.net, as the use of cookies is a necessary part of the vasundhara.net technology. vasundhara.net uses cookies only to:

  * Provide its services
  * Deliver content specific to visitor/member interests
  * Save your password (so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit different pages on our site) and for other purposes.

**Please note:** Cookies are used only to recollect information sent to your computer from vasundhara.net. We CANNOT access any information not sent by vasundhara.net site. Some of our partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Changes in vasundhara.net privacy policy:** UEPL reserves right to amend the privacy policy of vasundhara.net. Users are advised to periodically check our privacy policy for any amends.  
Any sensitive information (such as a credit card number) provided during registration/order process information, is encrypted and is protected with the standard encryption software in the industry – SSL as practiced by respective payment gateway.  
Apart from using SSL encryption, vasundhara.net takes every measure in its power to protect sensitive information Some of the staff members at vasundhara.net are granted access to such personally identifiable information, needed for performing specific tasks (for example, a billing clerk or a customer service representative.)

**Vasundhara.net uses email extensively to help members. Members may receive emails for the following services:**

  * Response to your post/upload/article/comment/contribution of story etc.,
  * Newsletters with updates on the latest features on our site.
  * Announcements of special events
  * Special offers or promotions at vasundhara.net of partner sites 

You are automatically subscribed to all of the above services while registering with vasundhara.net. If you wish to unsubscribe or manage subscriptions to one or more of the above services, you may do so at any time. 

####  Contact vasundhara.net: 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of vasundhara.net, or your dealings with this Web site, please email us or contact us at.

**contactus@vasundhara.net  
Vasundhara Kutumbam  
Eenadu complex  
Somajiguda   
Hyderabad 500 082  
040-23318181 Ext 6713  
**

You are also advised to peruse terms and conditions.
